Zbigniew Stolarski

I am a Frontend Developer with 2 years of experience creating modern and responsive websites from scratch using top frontend frameworks. I am doing my best to create a user-oriented website that is accessible and with fast loading speed. I'm using my experience to pick the right tools to create a design that suits your specific requirement.

Work History

2021-09

Frontend Developer

- present

Esri Polska, Warsaw, Poland

https://www.esri.pl/

Global market leader in GIS

 Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.

2019-09 - 2021-07

Frontend Developer

InCore Service, Warsaw, Poland

www.incpraca.pl

Online job agency

- IncPraca app development
- Implementation of website mockups in Figma software.
- Implementation of dozens of website components in the Vue.js framework.
- Testing of created components in the Jest framework.
- Technologies and tools used in the project:
- Vue.js, Jest, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Webpack, jQuerry, Sass, Bootstrap, git, npm, GitHub, Gitea, Bitbucket, Jira, Slack, Visual Studio Code

Projects

2022-03

Social App

- 2022-05

https://fir-508b2.web.app/

Social media app

Fully-featured social media application using React, Firebase, Redux,

Express, and Material-UI.

2021-01

Portfolio

- 2021-02

www.zbigniewstolarski.pl

This is a website about me. It contains all my projects and easy contact with me.

- · Created with Vue.js styled with Bootstrap.
- Contact form handled by a PHP file.

2021-02

Pikachu Game

- 2021-03

www.zbigniewstolarski.pl/#/furryGame

The game is about catching Pikachu without hitting the edges of the board.

The ability to work on arrays and objects was essential.

2021-03

Game Of LIfe

- 2021-04

www.zbigniewstolarski.pl/#/gameOfLife

The game presents the process of cells reproduction. It is a zero-player game, meaning that its evolution is determined by its initial state, requiring no further input.



Personal Info

Phone

797896967

Fmail

stolarskizbigniew93@gmail.com

Website

www.zbigniewstolarski.pl

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/ZbigniewCL

Citizenship

Polish

Skills

Vue.js, React.js, Jest, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Webpack, jQuerry, Sass, Bootstrap, git

Software

Visual Studio Code

Windows

Linux

Languages

English



Hobby

- Internet of Things
- Arduino programming
- Drone filming
- · Website Applications

Education